export const chapter = "Chapter -22: Fair Play";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "What is the initial reason for the conflict between Jumman and his aunt?",
          optionA: "Jumman's refusal to take care of his aunt",
          optionB: "Jumman's wife's indifference towards the old lady",
          optionC: "Jumman's decision to transfer the property to his aunt",
          correctAnswer: "Jumman's wife's indifference towards the old lady",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why does the old lady decide to take her case to the village Panchayat?",
          optionA: "She wants to seek revenge against Jumman",
          optionB:
            "She believes the Panchayat can bring justice to her situation",
          optionC: "She wants to expose Jumman's wrongdoing to the villagers",
          correctAnswer:
            "She believes the Panchayat can bring justice to her situation",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Who among the villagers supports the old lady in her case?",
          optionA: "Everyone sympathizes with her",
          optionB: "Only Algu Choudhary sympathizes with her",
          optionC: "None of the villagers support her",
          correctAnswer: "Only Algu Choudhary sympathizes with her",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How does Jumman react when the old lady requests a monthly allowance?",
          optionA: "He agrees to provide the allowance willingly",
          optionB: "He becomes indifferent and refuses to comply",
          optionC: "He apologizes and tries to mend the relationship",
          correctAnswer: "He becomes indifferent and refuses to comply",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why does Algu Choudhary initially hesitate to support the old lady at the Panchayat?",
          optionA: "He is afraid of going against his best friend, Jumman",
          optionB: "He does not believe in the Panchayat system",
          optionC: "He thinks the old lady is exaggerating her problems",
          correctAnswer:
            "He is afraid of going against his best friend, Jumman",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the outcome of the Panchayat regarding Jumman and his aunt's dispute?",
          optionA: "Jumman is asked to apologize to his aunt",
          optionB: "Jumman is ordered to pay a monthly allowance to his aunt",
          optionC: "The property is transferred back to the old lady",
          correctAnswer:
            "Jumman is ordered to pay a monthly allowance to his aunt",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What unfortunate event occurs in Algu Choudhary's life after the resolution of Jumman's case?",
          optionA: "His house catches fire",
          optionB: "One of his bullocks dies",
          optionC: "He falls seriously ill",
          correctAnswer: "One of his bullocks dies",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why does Algu Choudhary decide to bring the case to the Panchayat for the second time?",
          optionA: "Sahu refuses to return the bullock",
          optionB: "Sahu fails to pay the promised amount",
          optionC: "Algu wants to seek revenge against Jumman",
          correctAnswer: "Sahu fails to pay the promised amount",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Who does Sahu nominate as the head Panch in the second case involving Algu and Sahu?",
          optionA: "Jumman",
          optionB: "Algu Choudhary",
          optionC: "The old lady",
          correctAnswer: "Jumman",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How does Jumman conduct himself as the head Panch during Algu and Sahu's case?",
          optionA: "He seeks revenge against Algu",
          optionB: "He remains impartial and delivers a just decision",
          optionC: "He supports Sahu without considering the facts",
          correctAnswer: "He remains impartial and delivers a just decision",
        },
   ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Jumman and Algu Choudhary had such a strong bond of friendship that when either of them went away from the village, the ________ looked after his family.",
          optionA: "Neighbors",
          optionB: "Panchayat",
          optionC: "Relatives",
          correctAnswer: "Neighbors",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Jumman's old aunt transferred her property to him with the understanding that he would look after her. However, the arrangement worked well for a couple of years, and then the situation ________.",
          optionA: "Improved",
          optionB: "Deteriorated",
          optionC: "Remained unchanged",
          correctAnswer: "Deteriorated",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The old lady, Jumman's aunt, decided to take her case to the village Panchayat after facing indifference from Jumman and his wife. She sought support from the villagers and spoke to them, explaining her case and seeking their ________.",
          optionA: "Sympathy",
          optionB: "Laughter",
          optionC: "Advice",
          correctAnswer: "Sympathy",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Algu Choudhary, when approached by the old lady, initially hesitated to support her at the Panchayat due to his strong ________ with Jumman.",
          optionA: "Friendship",
          optionB: "Enmity",
          optionC: "Indifference",
          correctAnswer: "Friendship",
        },
        {
          question:
            "During the Panchayat, Jumman shamelessly asked his aunt to nominate the head of the Panchayat. The old lady nominated Algu Choudhary, and Jumman pretended to ________ this unexpected piece of luck.",
          optionA: "Hide",
          optionB: "Celebrate",
          optionC: "Regret",
          correctAnswer: "Celebrate",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The second conflict involved Algu Choudhary and Sahu, a cart driver. Sahu bought a bullock from Algu, and when the bullock died within a month, Sahu refused to pay, claiming the bullock brought ________.",
          optionA: "Joy",
          optionB: "Luck",
          optionC: "Ruin",
          correctAnswer: "Ruin",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Algu Choudhary decided to bring the case to the Panchayat for the second time, and Sahu proposed Jumman as the head Panch. Algu had no choice but to ________.",
          optionA: "Accept",
          optionB: "Reject",
          optionC: "Propose someone else",
          correctAnswer: "Accept",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Jumman, now the head Panch, realized his responsibility as a judge and the dignity of his office. He decided not to let his personal feelings come in the way of speaking the truth and doing ________.",
          optionA: "Injustice",
          optionB: "Revenge",
          optionC: "Justice",
          correctAnswer: "Justice",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Panchayat decided that Sahu should pay Algu the price of the bullock because when Sahu bought the bullock, it suffered from no disability or disease, and the death of the bullock was ________.",
          optionA: "Predictable",
          optionB: "Unfortunate",
          optionC: "Beneficial",
          correctAnswer: "Unfortunate",
        },
        {
          question:
            "After the resolution of the second case, Jumman approached Algu, realizing the true meaning of being a Panch. He acknowledged that a Panch has neither friend nor enemy and knows only ________.",
          optionA: "Revenge",
          optionB: "Justice",
          optionC: "Enmity",
          correctAnswer: "Justice",
        },
   ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Jumman and Algu Choudhary had a strained relationship due to a property dispute.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The old lady, Jumman's aunt, transferred her property to him with the understanding that he would look after her, and this arrangement worked well for many years.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Algu Choudhary initially refused to support the old lady at the Panchayat due to his enmity with Jumman.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "During the Panchayat, Jumman shamelessly asked his aunt to nominate the head of the Panchayat.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Sahu, the cart driver, willingly paid Algu Choudhary the price of the bullock after it died within a month.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Jumman, as the head Panch, remained impartial and delivered a just decision during Algu and Sahu's case.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The old lady, after the resolution of the first case, became friends with Jumman again.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Algu Choudhary nominated Jumman as the head Panch in the second case involving Sahu.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Panchayat decided that Jumman should apologize to his aunt for the mistreatment.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The conflicts between the characters in the story were primarily resolved through personal revenge rather than the Panchayat system.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
   ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
